halaltrip.com 2019-04-20

# Halal Trip - Privacypolicy Home

This privacy statement describes how we use the information you provide to us or we gather from you while you use the HalalTrip online services, as provided by HalalTrip Pte Ltd. (“HT” or “us” or “we”). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. It is important that you have a comprehensive understanding of our information collection and usage practices. In your best interests, we advise that you read each provision of this Privacy Policy. By visiting, accessing or using the HalalTrip website (halaltrip.com), mobile applications and all associated services, features and content (“Service” or “Services”), you acknowledge agreement to this Privacy Policy. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy. We retain the exclusive right to amend this Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way that we use your personal information, we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our Site. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

#### The information we collect

### We collect and use your information below to provide, understand and better improve our Services:

**Basic Account Information:** When you register an account with us, you must provide unique identifiers such as user name, email address and password. Your username is always publicly listed, including on your profile page and in search results. You may choose to provide additional personal information such as your profile image, address, gender, phone number, bio and country to customize your profile.

**Information and Content you Provide:** We collect content, communications and other information you provide when you use our Services, including when you register for an account, create or share content, and message or communicate with others on our platforms. This can include information in or about the content you provide (e.g. metadata), such as location of a photo or the date a file was created. For instance, when you share a dish, restaurant or attractions, all information you provide is stored on our database and made visible to the other users, including your reviews and comments. Additional information from third party services such as Facebook and Google may be provided by you to us to facilitate and ease your login and account setup process.

**Your Usage:** When you interact with us, we collect information about how you use our Service, such as what content you viewed, which features you use, the actions you take, and which areas of our Service or Site you visited. This includes your interactions with other users, as well as downloads you made from our Service or Site.

**Information about Transactions made on our Services:** If you use our service for purchases like booking of travel packages, hotels, and HalalTrip pass, we may collect additional information to authenticate your details such as contact details, flight details, passenger details and passport details to facilitate a seamless booking experience for you. Past transaction history with us will be stored in our database and can be accessed in your account under “My Flights” and “My Purchase”. Also, when you contact us, we will require to collect your name, email and phone number to follow up with your queries and/or concerns.

**Location Information:** We may receive information about your locations. For instance, you may choose to set your location by sharing with us your GPS location so that you can use our features like finding mosques, prayer rooms and attractions near you, or receive notifications on prayer timings and the qibla direction at your location.

**Additional Information:** We collect device information, information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

If you contact us, we also collect the information you provide that details the nature of your question or problem to enhance the quality of our Service. If you invite a friend by email to our Service through the Service, we will send your friend an invitation email inviting him or her to visit the Service and/or Site. We store this information for the sole purpose of sending this invitation email. Your friend may contact us at info@halaltrip.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

#### We use this information to:

  * Administer your account.
  * Complete your bookings of travel packages, hotels and/or HalalTrip pass.
  * Send product updates or warranty information.
  * Send you a newsletter (You may opt-out of receiving our newsletter or marketing emails from us by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each newsletter or marketing email. You can also contact us at info@halaltrip.com to unsubscribe).
  * Send you marketing communications.
  * Provide, personalize and improve our Services, Site and marketing efforts.
  * Conduct research and analysis.
  * Communicate with you by responding to your questions and concerns.

We keep your personal data only for as long as necessary to provide you with the Services and for legitimate and essential business purposes (e.g. maintaining and improving the performance of our Services, making data-driven business decisions to introduce new products and/or services to you).

We may keep some of your personal data for as long as you are a user of the Services. If you request, we will delete or anonymise your personal data so that it can no longer identify you, unless we are legally allowed or required to maintain certain personal data (e.g. fraud prevention or to maintain user security).

#### How Your Information Is Protected

We maintain data handling and storage practices and procedures that are designed to ensure the integrity and confidentiality of the personally identifiable information and email addresses submitted to us. We have implemented various policies to guard against unauthorised access and unnecessary retention of personal data in our systems. However, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage can ever be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we are unable to provide any absolute assurances in this regard or guarantee that the information you provide to us will be secure at all times, and we cannot be responsible for any event arising from unauthorised access to your personal information. We will therefore not be held responsible for events arising from third parties gaining unauthorized access to your personal information. The information will be protected in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy and will be subject to any disclosure requirements contained in any applicable law.

Please note also that we may use overseas facilities to process or back up information. As a result, we may transfer to and store your personal information at our overseas facilities. However, this does not change any of our commitments to safeguard your privacy. All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors' personal data.

#### When we may disclose your personal information

### We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed except: 

  * As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process.
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
  * If we are in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

We may disclose your personal information on occasion to third parties who work with us. Some of these third parties may be located outside your home country. The information will be protected in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy and will be subject to any disclosure requirements contained in any applicable law. If we wish to use your personal data for a new purpose, we will update our privacy policy accordingly and we will offer you the means to consent to this new purpose through email.

#### Children

Children are not eligible to use the Service and we ask that minors (anyone under the age of 16) not submit any personal information to us. We do not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 16 or permit them to use our Service. If we learn that we have collected the personal data of minors under the age of 16, we will take reasonable steps to delete the personal data, which may include the deletion of account under our Service.

#### Your Rights

The new European data protection law, called the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), gives individuals certain rights in relation to personal data.

### The rights given to you are:

  * Right to be informed about how your personal information is being used
  * Right to access the personal information we hold about you
  * Right to request that we amend or update your personal data where it is inaccurate or incomplete
  * Right to request that we delete your data, stop processing or collecting it
  * Right to stop direct marketing messages or withdraw consent for other content-based processing at any time

If you wish to access the personal data which you have provided to us and which we may hold in our database, you can ask us by sending us an email at info@halaltrip.com. We will provide you with a readable copy of the record which we maintain incorporating your personal data within a week of your request. We may require proof of your identify but we will provide the information without any charge.

If you wish to delete your account, you may do so from your account settings. If you have trouble doing so, you may contact us directly at info@halaltrip.com. Please note that we will keep a backup copy for a reasonable period of time to prevent fraud and if you change your mind.

#### Cookies

We use cookies when you visit our Site and/or Services. A cookie is a small file containing a small piece of data that is stored on your computer or mobile device. These cookies are used to not only improve the website but also allow you to be recognized as the same user across different pages of a website or when you use the app. In order to personalize your experience with us, the types of information that we collect through cookies include IP address; device ID; viewed pages; browser type; browsing information; operating system; internet service provider; timestamp; the referring URL; and features used or activities engaged in within the website/apps.

In addition, these cookies help to authenticate your account, ensure security and integrity of website and products, provide insights and monitor aggregate usage patterns to better improve our performance, website features and services. Additionally, it helps us remember your location and language preferences to better serve you. Please note that we will not track your information when you visit our site.

By using our site, you agree to us placing these cookies on your device and accessing them when you visit the site in the future. If you want to delete any cookies that are already on your computer, the “Help” section in your browser should provide instructions on how to locate the file or directory that stores cookies. Please note that by deleting or disabling future cookies, some of our services may not function properly and you might not be able to take advantage of certain functions on our site. For more information about cookies, please visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/. 

#### Privacy Support

Thank you for reading our Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about security on our Service or Site, you can contact us at info@halaltrip.com. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active, or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, contact us at info@halaltrip.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

You can contact us about this privacy statement by email or by writing at the address below:

HalalTrip Pte Ltd  
80 Changi Road,  
#05-12 Centropod,  
Singapore 419715  
Email: info@halaltrip.com
